<gallery>
	<art>
		<artist name="Vincent Van Gogh">
			<image path="Images/painters/van_gogh.jpg" />
			<info>
				Vincent Willem van Gogh (30 March 1853 - 29 July 1890) was a
				Dutch Post-Impressionist painter who is among the most famous
				&amp; influential figures in the history of Western art. In just
				over a decade he created approximately 2100 artworks, including
				around 860 oil paintings, most of them in the last two years of
				his life. They include landscapes, still lifes, portraits &amp;
				self-portraits, &amp; are characterised by bold, symbolic colours,
				&amp; dramatic, impulsive &amp; highly expressive brushwork that
				contributed to the foundations of modern art. Van Gogh became 
				famous after his suicide at age 37, which years of poverty
				&amp; mental illness.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Leonardo Da Vinci">
			<image path="Images/painters/davinci.jpg" />
			<info>
				Leonardo di ser Piero da Vinci (15 April 1452 - 2 May 1519) was an
				Italian polymath of the High Renaissance who was active as a painter,
				draughtsman, engineer, scientist, theorist, sculptor, &amp; architect.
				While his fame initially rested on his achievements as a painter, he
				has also become known for his notebooks, in which he made drawings &amp;
				notes on a variety of subjects, including anatomy, astronomy, botany,
				cartography, painting, &amp; paleontology. Leonardo is widely regarded to
				have been a genius who epitomized the Renaissance humanist ideal, &amp;
				his collective works comprise a contribution to later generations of
				artists matched only by that of his younger contemporary Michelangelo.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Michelangelo">
			<image path="Images/painters/michelangelo.jpg" />
			<info>
				Michelangelo di Lodovico Buonarroti Simoni (6 March 1475 - 18 February
				1564), known mononymously as Michelangelo, was an Italian sculptor,
				painter, architect, &amp; poet of the High Renaissance. Born in the Republic
				of Florence, his work was inspired by models from classical antiquity &amp;
				had a lasting influence on Western art. Michelangelo's creative abilities
				&amp; mastery in a range of artistic arenas define him as an archetypal
				Renaissance man, along with his rival &amp; elder contemporary, Leonardo da
				Vinci. Given the sheer volume of surviving correspondence, sketches, &amp;
				reminiscences, Michelangelo is one of the best-documented artists of the 16th
				century.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Raphael">
			<image path="Images/painters/raffaello.jpg" />
			<info>
				Raffaello Sanzio da Urbino (March 28 or April 6, 1483 - April 6, 1520), now
				generally known in English as Raphael, was an Italian painter &amp; architect
				of the High Renaissance. His work is admired for its clarity of form, ease
				of composition, &amp; visual achievement of the Neoplatonic ideal of human
				grandeur. Together with Leonardo da Vinci &amp; Michelangelo, he forms the
				traditional trinity of great masters of that period.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Rembrandt">
			<image path="Images/painters/rembrandt.jpg" />
			<info>
				Rembrandt Harmenszoon van Rijn (15 July 1606 - 4 October 1669), usually simply
				known as Rembrandt, was a Dutch Golden Age painter, printmaker, &amp; draughtsman.
				An innovative &amp; prolific master in three media, he is generally considered one
				of the greatest visual artists in the history of art. It is estimated Rembrandt
				produced a total of about three hundred paintings, three hundred etchings, &amp;
				two thousand drawings.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Claude Monet">
			<image path="Images/painters/monet.jpg" />
			<info>
				Oscar-Claude Monet (14 November 1840 - 5 December 1926) was a French painter &amp;
				founder of impressionist painting who is seen as a key precursor to modernism,
				especially in his attempts to paint nature as he perceived it. During his long
				career, he was the most consistent &amp; prolific practitioner of impressionism's
				philosophy of expressing one's perceptions before nature, especially as applied
				to plein air (outdoor) landscape painting. The term "Impressionism" is derived
				from the title of his painting Impression, soleil levant, exhibited in 1874
				(the "exhibition of rejects") initiated by Monet &amp; his associates as an
				alternative to the Salon.
			</info>
		</artist>
	</art>

	<music>
		<artist name="David Bowie">
			<image path="Images/Music/DavidBowie.jpg" />
			<info>
				David Robert Jones (8 January 1947 - 10 January 2016), known
				professionally as David Bowie was an English singer, songwriter,
				musician, &amp; actor. He is regarded as one of the most influential
				musicians of the 20th century. Bowie was acclaimed by critics &amp;
				musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s.
				His career was marked by reinvention &amp; visual presentation, &amp;
				his music &amp; stagecraft had a significant impact on popular music.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Michael Jackson">
			<image path="Images/Music/MCJackson.jpg" />
			<info>
				Michael Joseph Jackson (August 29, 1958 - June 25, 2009) was an
				American singer, songwriter, dancer, &amp; philanthropist. Known
				as the "King of Pop", he is regarded as one of the most significant
				cultural figures of the 20th century. During his four-decade career,
				his contributions to music, dance, &amp; fashion, along with his
				publicized personal life, made him a global figure in popular culture.
				Jackson influenced artists across many music genres. Through stage &amp;
				video performances, he popularized complicated street dance moves such
				as the moonwalk, which he named, as well as the robot.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Eminem">
			<image path="Images/Music/Eminem.jpg" />
			<info>
				Marshall Bruce Mathers III (born October 17, 1972), known professionally as
				Eminem is an American rapper. He is credited with popularizing hip hop in Middle
				America &amp; is often regarded as one of the greatest rappers of all time. His
				global success &amp; acclaimed works are widely regarded as having broken racial
				barriers for the acceptance of white rappers in popular music. While much of his
				transgressive work during the late 1990s &amp; early 2000s made him a controversial
				figure, he came to be a representation of popular angst of the American underclass
				&amp; has been cited as an influence by &amp; upon many artists working in various genres.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Lady Gaga">
			<image path="Images/Music/LadyGaga.jpg" />
			<info>
				Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta (March 28, 1986), known professionally as Lady Gaga,
				is an American singer, songwriter, &amp; actress. She is known for her image reinvention
				&amp; versatility in the entertainment industry. Gaga began performing as a teenager,
				singing at open mic nights &amp; acting in school plays. She studied at Collaborative Arts
				Project 21, through the New York University Tisch School of the Arts, before dropping out
				to pursue a career in music. Gaga had her breakthrough in 2008 with her debut studio album,
				The Fame, &amp; its chart-topping singles "Just Dance" &amp; "Poker Face". The album was later
				reissued to include the extended play The Fame Monster (2009), which yielded the successful
				singles "Bad Romance", "Telephone", &amp; "Alejandro".
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Celine Dion">
			<image path="Images/Music/CelineDion.jpg" />
			<info>
				Celine Marie Claudette Dion CC OQ (30 March 1968) is a Canadian singer. Referred to as the
				"Queen of Power Ballads", she is noted for her powerful &amp; technically skilled vocals.
				Her music has incorporated genres such as pop, rock, R&amp;B, gospel, &amp; classical music.
				Her recordings have been mainly in English &amp; French, although she has also sung in
				Spanish, Italian, German, Latin, Japanese, &amp; Chinese.
			</info>
		</artist>

		<artist name="Steve Perry">
			<image path="Images/Music/StevePerry.jpg" />
			<info>
				Stephen Ray Perry (born January 22, 1949) is an American singer &amp; songwriter. He wasthe
				lead singer &amp; frontman of the rock band Journey during their most successful years from
				1977 to 1987, &amp; again from 1995 to 1998. He also wrote/co-wrote several Journey hit
				songs. Perry had a successful solo career between the mid-1980s &amp; mid-1990s, made sporadic
				appearances in the 2000s, &amp; returned to music full-time in 2018.
			</info>
		</artist>
	</music>

	<movies>
		<movie name="The Terminator">
			<image path="Images/movies/Terminator.jpg" />
			<info>
				The Terminator is a 1984 American science fiction action film directed
				by James Cameron. It stars Arnold Schwarzenegger as the Terminator, a
				cybernetic assassin sent back in time from 2029 to 1984 to kill Sarah
				Connor (Linda Hamilton), whose unborn son will one day save mankind from
				extinction by Skynet, a hostile artificial intelligence in a
				post-apocalyptic future. Kyle Reese (Michael Biehn) is a soldier sent back
				in time to protect Sarah. Casting: [Arnold Schwarzenegger, Michael Biehn,
				Linda Hamilton, Paul Winfield, Lance Henriksen, Bess Motta, Rick Rossovich,
				Earl Boen]
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Oppenheimer">
			<image path="Images/movies/Oppenheimer.jpg" />
			<info>
				Oppenheimer is a 2023 epic biographical thriller film written &amp; directed
				by Christopher Nolan. It stars Cillian Murphy as J. Robert Oppenheimer, the
				American theoretical physicist credited for his role in the Manhattan Project—the
				World War II undertaking that developed the first nuclear weapons. The film chronicles
				the career of Oppenheimer, with the story predominantly focusing on his studies, his direction
				of the Manhattan Project during World War II, &amp; his eventual fall from grace
				due to his 1954 security hearing. Casting: [Cillian Murphy, Emily Blunt, Matt Damon,
				Robert Downey Jr., Florence Pugh, Josh Hartnett, Casey Affleck, Rami Malek]
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Forrest Gump">
			<image path="Images/movies/ForrestGump.jpg" />
			<info>
				Forrest Gump is a 1994 American comedy-drama film directed by Robert Zemeckis &amp;
				written by Eric Roth. It is based on the 1986 novel of the same name by Winston Groom
				&amp; stars Tom Hanks, Robin Wright, Gary Sinise, Mykelti Williamson &amp; Sally Field.
				The film follows several decades in the life of a slow-witted yet kindhearted Alabama
				man named Forrest Gump (Hanks) &amp; his experiences in the 20th-century United States.
				The film differs substantially from the novel. Casting: [Tom Hanks, Michael Conner Humphreys,
				Robin Wright, Hanna R. Hall, Gary Sinise, Mykelti Williamson, Sally Field, Haley Joel Osment,
				Peter Dobson]
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Batman">
			<image path="Images/movies/DarkKnight.jpg" />
			<info>
				The Dark Knight is a 2008 superhero film directed by Christopher Nolan from a
				screenplay co-written with his brother Jonathan. Based on the DC Comics superhero
				Batman, it is the sequel to Batman Begins (2005) and the second installment in
				The Dark Knight Trilogy. The plot follows the vigilante Batman, police lieutenant
				James Gordon, and district attorney Harvey Dent, who form an alliance to dismantle
				organized crime in Gotham City. Their efforts are derailed by the Joker, an
				anarchistic mastermind who seeks to test how far Batman will go to save the city
				from chaos. Casting: [Christian Bale, Michael Caine, Heath Ledger,
				Gary Oldman, Aaron Eckhart, Maggie Gyllenhaal, and Morgan Freeman]
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Joker">
			<image path="Images/movies/Joker.jpg" />
			<info>
				Joker is a 2019 American psychological thriller film directed by Todd Phillips.
				The film, stars Joaquin Phoenix as Joker. Set in 1981, it follows Arthur Fleck, a failed clown &amp;
				aspiring stand-up comic whose descent into mental illness &amp; nihilism inspires a violent
				countercultural revolution against the wealthy in a decaying Gotham City.Distributed by Warner Bros.
				Pictures, Joker was produced by Warner Bros. Pictures &amp; DC Films in association with
				Village Roadshow Pictures, Bron Creative &amp; Joint Effort. Casting: [Joaquin Phoenix, Robert
				De Niro, Zazie Beetz Frances Conroy Hannah Gross]
			</info>
		</movie>

		<movie name="Gladiator">
			<image path="Images/movies/Gladiator.jpg" />
			<info>
				Gladiator is a 2000 epic historical drama film directed by Ridley Scott and written
				by David Franzoni, John Logan, and William Nicholson. Crowe portrays Roman general Maximus Decimus
				Meridius, who is betrayed when Commodus, the ambitious son of Emperor Marcus Aurelius, murders his
				father and seizes the throne. Reduced to slavery, Maximus becomes a gladiator and rises through the
				ranks of the arena to avenge the murders of his family and his emperor. Casting: [Russell Crowe,
				Joaquin Phoenix, Connie Nielsen, Tomas Arana, Ralf Möller, Oliver Reed, Djimon Hounsou, Derek Jacobi,
				John Shrapnel, Richard Harris, Tommy Flanagan]
			</info>
		</movie>
	</movies>
</gallery>